# KHRANOVSKYI OLEKSII

Software Engineer

#### **SUMMARY**

Olekssi has a broad skill set ranging from full-stack development and distributed computing to blockchain technologies. He has had extensive experience with the Java and Node.js ecosystems as a software engineer at Evovor Technologies Inc and TargetAds Ltd. He has strong analytical skills and takes great care in communicating with clients to find the right solution for their needs.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **National Aviation University**

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng) 2018-2021

## **SKILLS**

Software Development Knowledge of PHP, HTML, CSS and Javascript/JQuery, Node.js, ReactJS, VueJS, TypeScript, Solidity, Web3, Rust and Solana Blockchain

- Development, DApp
  Development(NFT Marketplace, Defi)
- Awareness of the Web Development industry, and new technologies

## **PROFESSIONAL**

Able to organise own workload effectively and prioritise tasks Can quickly understand business requirements and then translate these into functional requirements Having a passion for customer service & responding quickly to enquiries Can manage multiple projects in a fastpaced, deadline-driven environment Adaptable and able to quickly pick up new techniques Understanding of W3C standards, web accessibility & best practice

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Full Stack Engineer**

TargetAds Inc | 2022 - 2023

Manage the schedules and calendars of the CEO and other senior executives

- Work with GCP and AWS services such as EC2, S3, and Lambda to deploy and scale web applications
- Use GitLab and GitHub for version control and collaborate with team members using JIRA, Asana and Slack

## Full Stack Developer

Evovor Technologies Inc | 2020 - 2022

Developed web applications using Laravel, Codelgniter, MySQL and

- JavaScript frameworks
  - Developed web applications using React, Vue.js, Node.js, Nest.js,
- MySQL and MongoDB( MERN, MEVN stack)
  Implemented RESTful APIs to enable communication between front-end
- and back-end systems

#### **Junior Front End Developer**

Evovor Technologies Inc | 2019 - 2020

Collaborate with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality web applications using React, Vue.js, Next.js, Tailwind CSS and Material UI Developed user-friendly interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks

## Intern Developer And Blockchain engineer

Evovor Technologies Inc | 2018 - 2019 Used Adobe Photoshop, Sketch, and Figma for UI design Developed user-friendly interfaces using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript

Developed DApp such as DeFi, Dex, NFT Marketplace, creating token and so on